Runner's knee runner's
knee is a condition characterized by pain behind or around
the kneecap. It is caused by overuse,
muscle imbalance and inadequate stretching. Symptoms include
pain under or around the kneecap, pain when
walking sprained ankle one
nil here in the 37th minute she is between two guatemalan
defenders and then goes down and stays down and
you will see why. The ligaments of the ankle holds the ankle
bones and joint in position. They protect the ankle
from abnormal movements such as twisting, turning and
rolling of the foot. A sprained ankle happens when the
foot twists, rolls or turns beyond its normal motions.
If the force is too strong, the ligaments can tear.
Symptoms include pain and difficulty moving the ankle,
swelling around the ankle and bruising.
Meniscus tear I think some of it was just
being scared, but this guy doesn't like you. Want to go
after Patrick each of your knees has two menisci c shaped
pieces of cartilage that act like a cushion between your
shin bone and your thigh bone.
A meniscus tear happens when you forcibly twist or rotate
your knee, especially when putting the pressure of your full
weight on it, leading to a torn meniscus. Symptoms include
stiffness and swelling, pain in your knee,
catching or locking of your knee rotator
cuff tear has a torn rotator cuff cuff go be traveling
to Los Angeles today to be examined by teen doctors on the
rotator cuff attaches the humerus to the shoulder blade and
helps to lift and rotate your arm.
A rotator cuff tear is caused by a fall onto your arm or
if you lift a heavy object too fast,
the tendon can partially or completely tear off of the
humerus. Head symptoms
include pain when lifting and lowering your arm,
weakness when lifting or rotating your arm,
pain when lying on the affected shoulder.
ACL tear here's Rosario on the brake now and watch.
Nerls go up with the left hand, block the shot, and then on
landing, there came the the ACL runs diagonally in the
middle of the knee and provides stability.
Anterior cruciate ligament tear occurs when your foot
is firmly planted on the ground and a sudden force hits your
knee while your leg is straight or slightly bent.
This can happen when you are changing direction rapidly,
slowing down when running or landing from a jump.
The ligament completely tears into two pieces,
making the knee unstable.
Symptoms include severe pain and tenderness in knee,
loss of full range of motion, swelling around the knee.